

KYLIE WEBER

UI DESIGNER



+31684729201



kylieweberdesigns@outlook.com



in www.linkedin.com/in/kylie-weber-b73a51197/



Lijnbaansgracht 335,1017XA Amsterdam

www.behance.net/kylieweberdesigns

PROFILE

Hello, I am Kylie. I'm a hospitality-professional-turned-UI designer. I have 7 years of hospitality and business management experience and I have an instinctive user experience mind-set that is present in everything I do. I want to design accessible products that strive to make a difference in today's world so that everyone can benefit from the wonderful word of UI design.

EDUCATION

Career Foundry

2019-2020

User Interface Design Certification

IUBH (Bad Honnef)

2013-2017

B.A Hospitality Mangement

UX SKILLS

User Personas Wireframing **User Testing** User Interviews Market Analysis

UI SKILLS

Visual Design Responsive Design Sketching Iconography iOS & Android Design Prototyping Mockup Design

SOFTWARE

Sketch Balsamiq InVision Squarespace Angle Basic HTML/CSS

LANGUAGES SKILLS

English (Fluent)

German (Intermediate)

Swahili (Intermediate)

WORK EXPERIENCE

FREELANCE UI/ WEB DESIGNER

2019-Present

Amsterdam, The Netherlands

As a junior designer, I take on design projects and create solutions to various interface problems. Some tasks include: Creating web designs for small size businesses, Creating Marketing & Advertising print designs & Logo Design. Some responsibilities result in contributing to re-design and re-branding efforts. as well as aiding in SEO optimizations.

UI DESIGNER- SAVE UP MOBLIE APP

2019-2020

CareerFoundry (Online Case Study)

Completed all UI/UX actions for a mobile money saving-tool. A few key tasks included: Conducted UX actions such as competitor analysis, user testing, wireframing & iterating designs based on user feedback.

Responsible for the final UI design based on all initial brief, UX findings, and current market trends.

WEB DESIGNER

2018-2019

Wicks & Wishes Limited (Nairobi, Kenya)

A candle-making startup where my responsibilities were; creating a variety of online content & assisting in Marketing & PR efforts. Other tasks included: designing the company website, generating social media content, logo & brand design as well as approving all print designs.

HOTEL OPERATIONS MANAGER

2017-2019

Echo Villas Watamu (Watamu, Kenya)

Managed a private eco-friendly hotel on the Kenyan Coast. Taking part in community projects & improving hotel operations resulting in a 98% guest satisfaction rating. Some key operation responsibilities were: Reporting & managing all financial operations as well as leading all sales, marketing & advertising efforts. Actively took part in guest relations, all food & beverage activities & was responsible for recruitment, and work scheduling.